Right now, whatever satan might have used, in whichever way,
to connect you to himself - immorality, weaknesses, bad habits,
whatever situation you are facing,
these are things satan uses to connect us to himself.
This is what we want to fight against now.
Remember, the word you are about to speak is not yours.
Right now, open your lips and begin to disconnect yourself.
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself,
you demon - out!
Say out!
Face your neighbour!
Whatever demon, evil spirit in your life - out, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever atom, whatever trace of demon, evil spirit - out, in the name of Jesus!
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever evil spirit, demon - in the name of Jesus, out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
Remain silent.
I want you to face your neighbour and hold your neighbour's hand.
Face your neighbour.
Whatever satan, demon, might have used to connect you to himself -
be disconnected!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Every constant experience you are having of that bondage - be loosed!
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Every constant experience - it could be sickness, disease
affliction, hardship, poverty - be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips and begin to loose it.
Every constant experience you are having of that bondage - it could be sickness,
affliction, disease, hardship.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to cover everything that has to do with you with the blood of Jesus Christ.
I cover my family with the blood of Jesus.
I cover my home with the blood of Jesus.
I cover my finances with the blood of Jesus.
I cover my business with the blood of Jesus!
I cover my marital life with the blood of Jesus!
I cover my career with the blood of Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Cover your home with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your partner with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your nation with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your friends with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your relations with the blood of Jesus!
Cover them with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your direction with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your thoughts with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your reasoning with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your looking with the blood of Jesus!
Cover them with the blood of Jesus!
Remember your nation, your country - cover them with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your leaders with the blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 30/06/2018